孩子们  有时候在人生中  只是不经意的一瞥
Kids,sometime in life you've seen someone
你便立即知道
And you just instantly know
这就是你一直在寻觅的那个人
This is the person for you.
它可以在任何地方发生
It can happen anywhere.
即便是在一个去除纹身的小诊所的候诊室里
Even the waiting room of a tattoo removal clinic.
当我碰到丝戴拉的时候  这种感觉油然而生
And that's what happened when I met... ...stella.
蝴蝶形臀纹
Ah,the butterfly tramp stamp.
这可是我的拿手项目
My bread and butter.
我猜这跟糟糕的分手
So I'm guessing that the real story
还有酒精有关吧
Involves a bad breakup and some booze.
除非这是个帮派的纹身
Unless it's a gang tattoo,
如果是那样的话  我想是时候换个帮派了
In which case,i think it's time to find a new gang.
不  只是一开始我认为有个
No,i just thought it would be cool
毛毛虫的纹身会很酷
To get a caterpillar tattoo,
过了几周  不知道怎么搞得  突然间它就破蛹了...
And then a few weeks went by,and all of a sudden...
经过十次一小时的疗程就可以把这个去除
Well,i can get rid of it in ten one-hour sessions,
不过我得提醒你激光手术会很疼的哦
But,i should warn you,laser surgery's very painful.
那你就会发现
Well,i think you'll find
我特别能忍受疼痛
I have a very high tolerance for pain.
就在昨晚  我看完了一部超烂的电影
Just last night,i sat through the worst movie ever made.
九号行星外层空间计划(史上最烂电影的榜首)
Oh,plan 9 from outer space?
不  比这个更烂  命运之手(美国60年代恐怖片)
No, the worst movie--Hands of fate.
我可是上过医学院的医生
Uh,i'm a doctor,went to medical school.
相信我一定是九号行星这部比较烂  如果你不相信我
It's plan 9. if you don't believe me,
帕梅拉剧院现在就有在放映这个片子
It's playing down at the pamela theater.
那我可真不相信你  医生
Uh-huh. I don't believe you,doctor.
那你今晚有什么安排
Well,what are you doing tonight?
你好
hello.
好啊  泰德
Hey,ted
把钱包收起来吧  今天晚上我请客
Hey,put that away. tonight's on me.
不  还是不要了...
Oh,no,no,don't...
别客气  我坚持
Come on,i insist.
你人真好  谢谢啦
That's so nice. thank you.
朋友们  这是我朋友泰德
Hey,guys,this is my friend ted.
今晚他请客
He wants to pay.
哇  太感谢了
wow,thank you.
一  二  三  四
One,two,three,four.
出什么问题了吗
Is something wrong?
没有  只不过...
No,it's just,um...
我只不过是有点尴尬罢了
I'm just a little embarrassed.
我以为这是约会呢
I thought this was a date.
不过没事儿
But it's no big deal.
别担心
Don't worry about it.
怎么了
What's wrong?
泰德觉得尴尬  他以为这是个约会
Ted's embarrassed-- he thought this was a date.
泰德以为这是个约会
Ted thought this was a date.
丝戴拉  你知道泰德以为这是个约会吗
Stella,did you know ted thought this was a date?
什么  我不能和我的病人约会
What? I'm not allowed to date a patient.
这是美国医协的规定
It's an ama rule.
她不能和她的病人约会
She's not allowed to date patients.
这是医协的规定
It's an ama rule.
她不能和她的病人约会
She's not allowed to date patients.
这是医协的规定
It's an ama rule.
她不能和她的病人约会
She's not allowed to date...
我听见了
Yeah,i got it.
我们都听见了
We all got it.
泰德真是个冤大头
Ted's a schmuck.
-所以你买了所有人的票  -对呀  对呀
-And you bought all the tickets. -yeah,yeah.
是啊  你说对了
Hey,you were right.
这是我看电影以来最糟的经历
Worst movie-going experience ever.
当然  这跟电影本身没什么关系
Of course,it had nothing to do with the movie.
我感到很抱歉让你误会那是个约会
I am so sorry that you thought that was a date.
没关系
No,it's fine.
能和你在女友之夜一起出去也不错啊
I got to hang out with you on girls' night out.
好吧  如果你不能和你的病人约会
All right,so if you're not allowed to date a patient,
我就...  我就等到10个疗程结束后
I'll just... I'll wait until these ten session are up
再约你出去
And then I'll ask you out then.
那我还是提前先告诉你
Well, then,fair warning:
到时候我还是会说不行的
I'm going to say no.
是吗  我从你那儿感觉到的可不是这么回事
Really? I'm getting mixed signals from you.
我觉得你已经盯着我的臀部看了很久了
I feel like you've been staring at my ass for quite some time.
-为什么  你结婚了?  -不是
-What,you're married? -no.
-有男朋友了?  -不是
-Boyfriend? -no.
-是同性恋?  -不是
-Lesbian? -no.
-只和黑人约会?  -不是
-Only date black guys? -no.
那你现在可以充满信心的说
And yet you can say with absolute confidence
十周之后  如果我约你出去
That ten weeks from now,if I ask you out on a date,
-你的答案将是...  -不行
-Your answer will be... -no.
不行
No... hmm.
她说不的时候
What could she mean
究竟是什么意思
When she says no?
我不知道
I don't know,
总之是很神秘就对了
It is totally cryptic.
这离结束还早呢
This is far from over.
我是说还有十周的时间呢
We're talking ten weeks from now.
谁知道到时候她会怎么想呢
Who knows what she'll want then?
你知道十周后
Do you know what you're going to want
你午饭想吃什么吗
For lunch ten weeks from now?
炒牛肉酱  河虾鸡尾酒还有奶昔
Sloppy joe,shrimp cocktail and a milk shake.
泰德  你知道一个女人要决定是否
Ted,do you know how long it takes a woman
跟一个男人上床需要多久吗
To decide whether or not she's going to sleep with a guy?
8.3秒
8.3 seconds.
在那之后
After that,
她就心意已决
Her decision is made.
不会再改变主意了
She will not change her mind.
-这种说法太荒谬了  -是吗
-That's ridiculous. -is it?
描述一下你第一个8.3秒见到丝戴拉的情况
Describe your first 8.3 seconds with stella.
低腰蝴蝶纹身的  到你了
Lower back butterfly tattoo-- you're up.
那就算是我们开始不怎么顺利
So we got off to a rocky start.
对于有些人来说或许是个问题
That may be a problem for some guys,
但是随着时间的推移  我的优势就显现了
But I get better over time. right?
我可不像排行榜上前四十的歌曲
I'm not some top 40 song--
那么通俗易懂的
Easily digestible.
我是很复杂的
I'm complex.
需要时间和不断的聆听来反覆揣摩
I require time and multiple listens.
我是"天堂之梯"(齐柏林飞船乐队的名曲)
I'm "stairway to heaven."
罗杰・达尔崔会气得在棺材里打滚的(摇滚乐队谁人乐队主唱)
Wow,roger daltrey just rolled over in his grave.
我又弄错了  是不是
That's not the right guy,is it?
他还没死  是不是
He's not even dead,is he?
我觉得那很不错  泰德
I think that's great,ted.
你怎么想就怎么去做
You can do whatever you set your mind to.
事实上  你激发了我
In fact,you've inspired me.
我决定从今以后不咬指甲了
I'm going to stop biting my nails.
可亲爱的  你喜欢咬你的指甲啊
But,baby,you love biting your nails.
我知道  但我这是为了泰德而做的牺牲
I know,but I'm doing this for ted.
老天  这还真是很难啊
God,this is really hard.
给我十个疗程的时间
Give me ten sessions,
我要把那个"不行"变成"行"
I'm going to turn that "no" into a "yes."
-泰德  是吗  -恩啊
-Really,ted? -mm-hmm.
-你这么认为?  -恩啊
-You think so? -mmm.
那说说那天的疗程后来发生了什么
Well,tell me,how did the rest of that session go?
这个可能会有点疼哦
This is going to hurt a little.
没事  我能忍住
Yeah,well,i can handle pain.
有一次我在打网球...
This one time I was playing tennis,and...
不过去掉纹身的确是很疼
Yeah,but tattoo removal really hurts.
也许每个人都那么叫的吧
Everyone probably sounds like that.
医生  一切还顺利吧
Doctor,are you all right?
我怎么听到一个女人尖叫的声音
I heard a woman screaming in here. oh.
祝贺我还有九周美好的时光
Here's to nine more great sessions.
时间如流水
And so thess weeks went by.
第二个疗程的时候我告诉她
The second session I told her about how I spent a summer
我是怎样用一个夏天的时间来帮助贫民区的孩子
Working with inner-city kids.
第三疗程我们不停地说法语
The third session we both spoke nothing but french.
第四疗程我让她笑得
The fourth session I made her laugh so hard
从椅子上掉了下来
She fell out of her chair.
-到了第五个疗程  -还是"不行"
-So by the time the fifth session came around... -still no.
还不行
Still no.
到底是什么问题
What's up with that?
我是指  我都用上杂耍了
I mean,i juggled.
你杂耍?
You juggled?
我以为你本意是想打动她的
I thought you were trying to impress her.
你还玩魔术勒
You do magic.
杂耍哪里比魔术更逊啦
How is juggling any lamer than magic?
魔术才不逊勒
Magic's not lame.
我不明白  我是说
I don't get it. I mean...
这逊吗
Is this lame?
巴尼  不要
Oh,barney,no,no.
我们说过了  不许再在桌子上变火花
We said no fireballs at the table.
你到底是有什么问题
What the hell is wrong with you?
我们周围都是酒精  老兄
There's alcohol in here.
-巴尼  -我
-Barney... -I...
我们已经谈过这点了
We've talked about this.
你违反了消防安全规范
It's a fire code violation.
我知道  但是是泰德先惹我的
Yeah,but ted provoked me.
不  你现在得接受处罚
No,no,you are on a time-out.
-坐到那儿去  -但...  -过去
-Go sit over there. -but... -go!
不管怎么说  我就是不明白
Anyway... I don't get it.
她现在应该要喜欢上我了才对
She should be into me by now.
你能做到的  泰德
You know,you can do this,ted.
我原来说我不再咬指甲了
I said that I would stop biting my nails,
瞧  耶!
And kablam-ey.
这是个挑战
It's just a challenge.
当你用你的裸臀对着别人的脸的时候
It can't be easy to woo someone
想打动她  可不是这个容易的事情
While you're sticking your naked butt in their face.
对狒狒来说  它们就喜欢这个
Works for baboons.
这就是传说中的"展示"
It's called "presenting."
我就剩下四个疗程了
I got four sessions left.
肯定有什么方法是我还没发掘到的
Ther-there's got to be an angle I'm not seeing.
你是没有办法把"不行"变成"行"的  泰德
You can't turn a "no" into a "yes," ted.
这是不可能的
Can't be done.
那不一定  巴尼
I don't know,barney.
我的意思是  有时候坚持是有回报的
I mean,sometimes persistence pays off.
我后来就说了"行"的啊
I said "yes" eventually.
胡说  你才没有
No,you didn't.
你说的是  "不行  我们不能这样  我们是朋友"
You were like,"no,we can't,we're friends.
-这会破坏了我们这个小团体的气氛  -我指泰德
-It would mess up the dynamic of the group." -to ted.
好吧(巴尼也追过罗宾)
Oh,righ
等等
Wait a second.
慢着  我想到了
Wait a second,i got the angle.
先生  请不要冲着我喊
Sir,please don't yell at me,
因为如果有人冲着我喊的时候
Because when people yell at me,
我会忍不住想哭
I have a tendency to start crying.
请不要这样做
Please don't do it.
艾比  我以前就告诉过你
Abby,i've told you before. please.
如果他们对你无礼的话  就把电话挂了
When they're rude to you,hang up the phone.
加油
go on,
你能做到的  把电话挂了
You can do this,hang up.
艾比  挂掉它
abby,Hang it up.
我实在没有时间浪费...(电话的声音)
I am too busy to waste my time...
我很抱歉  我真希望
I'm sorry,i just wish
这些病人能对你仁慈一点
That some of the patients would be nicer to you.
那个接待
The receptionist.
那就是我的突破口
That's my way in.
我喜欢这主意
I like this.
可以勾引那个接待员
Seduce the receptionist.
这个计划相当不错
That's a great plan.
这不是我的计划
That's not the plan.
-而且这对我和丝戴拉能起到什么帮助  -谁?
-And how would that help me with stella? -who?
我有计划了
Here's the plan
你好啊  给你
hi. here.
我半路停下
I stopped--
你好  我半路停下买咖啡
Hi,i stopped for coffee
然后我想...  我也许可以给你带点什么
And i... and I thought I'd grab you something.
谢谢  你太好了
Oh,wow,thank you,that's so nice.
你就像个骑士
You're like a knight.
-我该叫你泰德爵士  -你说什么
-I should call you sir ted. -what?
没什么  没什么
Nothing. nothing.
真的很傻
It's really stupid.
姿曼医生  泰德来了
Um,dr. zinman,ted's here.
谢谢  谢谢  艾比
Thanks. thanks,abby.
现在我们就等着吧
And now we wait.
相当确定的是
And sure enough,
在第七阶段  她以全新的方式看我
By session seven,she saw me in a whole new light.
-我就要违反我的原则了  -尽管违反吧
-Okay,i'm about to break my big rule here. -break it.
好的
Okay.
艾比和她的教友
Abby goes bowling
每周三晚上都会去打保龄
With her church group every wednesday night...
她是真想约你  但是她害羞
and she really wanted to invite you,but she's too shy.
艾比是...?
Abby is...?
我的接待员
My receptionist.
那天你给她带咖啡了
You really made quite an impression on her
给她留下的影响很深
With the coffee the other day.
-我的意思是她不停地谈到你  -是艾比啊
-I mean,she has really not stopped talking about you.-oh,abby.
我还以为你说艾伦呢
I thought you said "alan."
-但是刚才你问我  艾比是...?  -是的
But you just said,"abby is...?" right.
你说的对  我以为我说的是艾伦
Right,i thought I said "alan."
谁是艾伦
Who's alan?
谁是艾比
Who's abby?
-我的接待员  -回答正确
-My receptionist. -exactly.
-怎么会这样  -泰德
-What is happening? -ted.
你只要想做你自己就行了  不要耍花招
You just got to be yourself,no more gimmicks.
你说得对  不要耍花招
You're right,no more gimmicks.
再来最后一个花招
One more gimmick.
你知道她的架子上有什么吗?
You know what's on her shelf?
励志书  《我的力量》
That self-help book the power of me.
我知道  我知道  但是我觉得
I know,i know,but I thought
如果我读了那本书  我就有新话题和她讨论了
If I read it,maybe we'd have something new to talk about.
真是一本不错的书
It's actually a great book.
它交给我完整记忆的力量
It taught me the power of complete memory.
我能借你的书看一下吗
Can I borrow your copy?
我不记得放在哪了
I left it somewhere. i forget.
你好
Hi.
泰德・莫斯比  预约姿曼医生
Ted mosby for dr. zinman.
你好  泰德  我会转告的
Hi,ted. I'll let her know.
用心灵感应?
Telepathically?
真有意思
That's funny.
这主意不但有意思而且很聪明  太棒了
That's funny,smart,and great.
很抱歉  我迟到了
I am so sorry that I am late.
我每天好像只有两分钟的午餐时间
I have,like,two minutes for lunch everyday.
-太疯狂了  -是的  我能理解
-It's crazy. -yeah,i understand.
我刚才看了看那个旧的书架
I was just,uh,checking out the old bookshelf here.
原来你也读《我的力量》
I see you've read the power of me.
-真有意思  -你说什么  不不
-It's funny... -what? oh,no.
你弄错了  我从来不读那种垃圾
No,no,no,no,no,i would never read that piece of crap.
大概是哪个病人落下的
Some patient left it here.
谢天谢地
Oh,thank god.
你说的太对了
I couldn't agree more.
那绝对是垃圾
That's total crap.
我看见有人坐地铁时看那本书
I see people reading that on the subway
我就想冲他喊  "找点事做吧  伙计!"
And I just want to shout,"get a life,people!"
-泰德  我找到你的书了  -什么
-Ted,i found your book. -what?
你的那本《我的力量》
Your book the power of me.
一定是不小心掉进垃圾桶了
I think you accidentally dropped it in the garbage.
什么  这...这不是我的
What? no,that's... that's not mine.
我从来没见过它
I've never seen that before in my life.
才怪  我刚看到你在大厅还读呢
No,you were reading it in the lobby.
不可能  你看错人了
Wha-- no,you have me confused with someone else.
不会的  看这里
No,no,look right here.
"泰德・莫斯比私人藏书"
"from the personal library of ted mosby."
是你吧
That's you.
泰德  我不得不说
Ted,i hate to say this,
是时候去搞那个接待员了
But I think it's "nail the receptionist" time.
我可不去搞那个接待员
I'm not gonna nail the receptionist.
泰德  每个男人从小的梦想
Ted,every little boy wants to grow up
就是搞上一名医生或者律师
To nail the doctor or the lawyer.
总得有人来眷顾一下接待员吧
Somebody's gotta nail the receptionist.
我喜欢的是丝黛拉
No. I like stella.
我听不下去了  泰德
Okay,i'm gonna stop you right there,ted.
你的小美人丝黛拉  有些美中不足
Your little stella is not so perfect.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我特意去诊所
I went down there
想亲眼目睹一下她的风采  是真的
And checked her out for myself. yeah.
在那过程中
And while I was down there,
我发现了一个秘密
I discovered that she had a secret,
天大的...耸人听闻的秘密
A terrible... terrible secret.
是什么
What? what is it?
稍候  我尿急
Hold on,i gotta pee.
我回来啦
Okay,i'm back.
最近工作怎样
What's going on at work?
到底是什么秘密?!
What's the big secret?!
好吧
Oh. oh,right.
我要预约姿曼医生
Hi,i'd like to see dr. zinman,please.
请问有什么具体事宜
Sure,what's it regarding?
我只是想看看她
Oh,i just want to see her.
目睹一下  看看她的相貌
Want to look at her,see what she looks like.
我...我不明白
I- I don't understand.
抱歉  我是否不小心
I'm sorry,did I accidentally
选了西班牙语?(原文为西班牙语,意思为按了2号键)
Oprima numero dos when I called?
你听的懂英语吧
Do you speak english?
我想见她
I want to see her!
先生  请不要吼我
Sir,please don't yell at me
别人吼我的时候
Because when people yell at me,
我就有一种想哭的感觉
I have a tendency to start crying.
你的资历证书编号多少
What are your credentials?!
请您不要吼了
Please don't do that. please.
我想知道我在和谁说话
I want to know who am I speaking with!
一开始她表现不错  美丽大方
At first she seemed great,beautiful,smart,
你这辈子都追不上她
Way out of your league.
但是  接下来的对话纯属意外
But then,i overheard this conversation.
我的祖父叫...我是家中最小...
...my grandfather's name-- I was the last-born so...
-艾比  我的催眠师打电话来了吗  -没有
Oh,abby,did my hypnotherapist call yet? no.
毛发狂这毛病什么时候才能摆脱掉
When am I going to kick this folliculaphilia?
毛发狂?
Folliculaphilia?
毛发狂
Folliculaphilia.
那是什么
What is that?
泰德  你的真命天女
Ted,your perfect woman
只对留胡子的男人感兴趣
Can only be attracted to men with moustaches.
傻子才会相信你
That is the stupidest thing I've ever heard.
不可能
That's not real.
是啊  这是我编出来的
You're right,ted. I'm just making that up.
我知道  谁会对毛发感兴趣呢
I know that you are because there's no such thing.
我有倒是会有一点
I got it a little bit.
我叫泰德・莫斯比  约了姿曼医生
Hi. uh,ted mosby for dr. zinman.
你好  泰德  胡子真好看
Oh,hi,ted. love the 'stache.
你看起来就像年轻时的汤姆・塞莱克(老友记中莫妮卡的老男友)
You look like a young tom selleck,
但是你比他帅一万倍
Only a million times handsomer.
姿曼医生  玛格南到了(汤姆・塞莱克的真名)
Dr. zinman,magnum's here to see you.
开玩笑的  真衰
Just kidding. stupid.
抱歉我晚了  例行的两分钟午餐
Sorry I'm late. typical two-minute lunch.
我们的疗程已经快...
So we are very close to getting...
这到底是为什么
Why? just why?
你忘了吗
Y- you don't remember?
我赌10美元
I'll bet anyone ten bucks
我会让泰德留胡子
I can get ted to grow a moustache.
我来赌
Uh... okay.
你把我倒数第2次的机会给弄砸了
You sabotaged my next to last chance with stella
只为10美元
For ten dollars?
我知道  这个忙我应该免费帮你
I know. I would've done it for free.
不对  你欠我10美元
But,no. you owe me ten bucks.
真欠抽  最后的疗程就在下周
This is awful. my-my tenth session is next week.
我依然会约她出来
I'm gonna ask her out,and she's gonna say
她依然会说出最衰的那个单音节  不行
The most demoralizing syllable in the english language-- no.
还是算了吧
You know what? just forget it.
我不会约她出来
I'm not even gonna ask her.
干嘛不  她喜欢你
No,you have to. she likes you.
她亲口说的...
She said so herself. i mean...
天哪  你也去看她了
Oh,my god,you went and saw her,too.
我发誓  我没去
I swear to you,i did not.
我老婆总是说我肘部太干燥
My wife's always getting on me about my dry elbows.
有人唠叨真好
So good to be in a relationship.
你生活中有这么一个人吗
Anyone special in your life?
又或者你会对某个人有兴趣?
Or maybe just someone you're interested in?
有吗  有吗(音节分开读强调泰德)
Interes-ted in?
你真应该去检查一下这个痣
You know,we should really get this mole checked out.
有点不正常
It's just a little irregular.
不正常?  妈呀
Irregular? oh,my god.
我完了  我毁了
This is it. it's all over.
我有一个患者
One of my patients has this
臀部上方纹了只小蝴蝶
Little butterfly tattoo at the bottom of his back.
先别管那个衰人了
Can you stop talking about your other patients?!
我生命都快垂危了  医生!
I'm dying here,woman!
好了  就算它是个小瘤
There you go. look,even if it is something,
也是良性的  不要担心
It's easily treatable,so try to relax. okay.
之前你说的那个
Hey,what was it you were saying before
纹蝴蝶的人  他怎么样
About the guy with the butterfly tattoo?
没...没什么
Oh,that... that's nothing.
只是有些感觉
It's just a little crush.
化验结果我会打电话告诉你
So I will be calling you with your results.
好的  谢谢
Oh. okay. thank you.
先生  你的书
Oh,sir,your book!
不会吧
no.
真的
Yes.
她说"有感觉"?
She said "crush"?
她和你谈到我?
And she was talking about me?
最后一疗程一点也不疼
That last session was the least painful of all.
-我享受着激光带来的灼热感  -完成了
-I savored every searing blast of that laser. -all done.
等待了10周的时刻终于来临  丝黛拉
The moment I'd waited ten weeks for had arrived. stella...
现在我已经不是你的患者
...now that I'm no longer your patient,
你愿意和我共进晚餐吗
Would you like to have dinner with me?
-泰德  你是一个好男人  -不要...
-Ted,you're a really nice guy... -oh,no.
认识你我很荣幸
It has been so great getting to know you.
我要杀了马修
I am gonna kill marshall.
过去的10周我过的很愉快
I've had so much fun these last ten weeks.
这比激光打的要疼多了
Oh,my god,this is worse than the laser.
-我有个女儿  -什么
-I have a daughter. -what?
她叫露西  今年八岁了
Her name's lucy. she's eight.
工作和照顾她  就是我生活的全部
Work and being with her,that's pretty much my life.
我的社交
My social calendar
仅限于每月当保姆照顾我女儿时
Is movie night with the girls once a month
和朋友看场电影
When I can get a sitter.
去年我没参加任何聚会
I mean,i've been to one party in the past year--
就连圣帕特里克节  都是提前退场
St. paddy's day-- it was awful,i left early.
说真的  我空闲时间
But,really,my only free time
只有那两分钟的午餐时间  所以...
Is the two minutes I get for lunch,so...
这就是我不去约会的原因
This is why I don't date.
泰德  我的时间
Ted,i only have time
只留给我生命中最重要的人  那个人就是露西
For one most important person in my life,and that's lucy.
不管怎么样  这段时间我过得很愉快
Anyway,it's been fun.
下次纹身的之前好好想想
Next time,think before you ink.
不过如果你下次起来的时候
But if you ever do wake up with,like,
发现你脚踝有个海豚纹身的话  打电话给我
A dolphin tattoo on your ankle,just give me a call.
结果就是这样
There it is--
她都有孩子了
She's a mom.
我们之间是不可能的
It's just not gonna happen.
伙计  真是遗憾了
Sorry,dude.
-吃个虾吧  -不用客气了
-Have a shrimp. -i'm good.
我觉得我只能怪我自己
I guess I got no one but myself to blame.
她一开始就告诉我了
She told me right from the start
她肯定会拒绝我的  而且肯定会...
She was gonna say no and sure enough...
等等
Wait a minute.
-你好  -好啊
-hi. -hi.
你其实没有真正拒绝我
You didn't actually say no.
怎么说
What do you mean?
那天你完全可以对我说"不"的
All this time you were,uh,you were supposed to say no,
但是你没有  我回顾了我们之前的谈话记录
But you didn't-- I checked the transcript.
所以我打算向你提议
So,here's what I'm proposing.
-呃  你只有两分钟  对吧  -对
-Uh... you only have two minutes,right? -right.
好的  你想...
Okay. you want to,uh...
跟我来个两分钟约会吗
Go on a two-minute date with me?
上一次两分钟约会的结果是我多了个女儿
Last two-minute date I had gave me a daughter.
-呃  那好吧  -太好了
-Um... okay. -great.
那...开始了  计程车!
And... go. taxi!
-泰德  我真的就只有两分钟  -我知道
-Ted,i seriously only have two minutes... -i know.
就是有120秒的时间
That's like 120 seconds.
麻烦到第22大道西380号
380 west 22nd,please.
麻烦快点  我们赶时间
And step on it. we're in a hurry.
第22大道西380号?  不就是...
380 west 22nd? that's...
这边请
Right this way.
谢谢你
Thank you,sir.
我一直就想来这个地方尝尝
You know,i have always wanted to try this place.
招牌沙拉
House salad.
-你的大学是?  -斯坦福大学
-So,college? -stanford.
我是卫斯理工会大学
wesleyan.
不错  你认识亚当・雷赛尔吗
Oh,good. do you know adam lazar?
-不认识  你认识史考特・克莱伯吗  -不认识
-No. scott crable? -mm-mm.
奶酪茄子
Eggplant parmesean.
-谢谢  -都切好了啊  不错
-Thanks. -oh,already cut up. nice.
可以把账单给我吗
Could we get the check please.
我们得在15秒之内看部电影
We're trying to make a movie in 15 seconds.
-当然可以  -好的  谢谢
-Of course. -okay,great.
你打算怎么跟我分担账单
Uh,how do you want to do this?
你刚吃了奶酪茄子
You had the eggplant parm.
我就点了一杯水  所以...
I only really had water so...
跟你开玩笑呢
I'm kidding.
好了  走吧
Okay. let's go.
计程车!
Taxi!
你觉得紧张吗
you nervous?
-有点儿  -完全看不出来
-A little bit. -you can't tell at all.
-那好吧  -你们好!
-Oh,good. yeah. hello!
第22大道西384号
384 west 22nd.
15秒时间  电影已经开演了吗
15 seconds. the movie's started.
没关系  我们只是错过预告而已
Nah,previews. we'll be fine.
时间刚刚好  它还没开始呢
Ah! just in time. it hasn't started yet.
我们看的是什么电影
So,what are we seeing?
命运之手
Manos: the Hands of Fate.
一整部电影吗
The whole thing?
只是一些主要片段而已
Only the important parts.
是我看过最糟糕的电影
Worst movie ever.
对  我都差点想走了  这种想法大概有5次之多
Yeah,i almost walked out,like,five times.
-我们时间分配得怎么样  -计程车!
-How we doing on time? -taxi!
我们还剩一点时间
We got a little time.
-好的  你想走着回去?  -为什么不
-Okay. do you want to walk it? -why not?
-你们好!  -再见!
-Hello! -good-bye!
你的女儿读几年级了
So what grade's your daughter in?
三年级了
Third grade.
哇  正值好年华啊
Ah! that's a good year.
的确  她很漂亮
Yeah,she's wonderful.
我只是希望我可以帮她戒烟
I just wish that I could get her to quit smoking,you know?
-什么  -开玩笑的
-What? -I'm kidding.
看  咖啡和甜点都准备好了
Oh. look,coffee and dessert?
知道吗  这附近总是不断在变化
You know,this neighborhood just keeps on changing.
这里曾是一间可爱的意大利小餐馆
This used to be a cute,little italian restaurant.
我知道  这才是纽约(暗指变化快)
I know. new york.
这是一个有生命的有机体  或是一个不停变化的挂毯
It's a living organism,an ever-changing tapestry.
时间过得真快  我们走吧
Ooh,look at the time. let's go.
-这个奶酪蛋糕真棒  -这花送给你吧
-Mmm,the cheesecake's amazing. -flowers?
我对花粉过敏
I'm allergic.
好的  看见没  我们开始了解对方了
Okay. see? we're getting to know each other.
斯戴拉  我过得很...  外卖给你
Stella,i had a lovely-- doggy bag?
斯戴拉  我过得很愉快
Stella,i had a lovely time.
我也是  泰德
Me,too,ted.
约会也不错  看见了吧
And... date. huh?
这样其实还不错嘛  对吗
That wasn't so bad,right?
没有冗长和尴尬的沉默
No lengthy,awkward silences.
甜点时间有点过长了  所以...
Dessert ran a little long,so...
我得把晚安吻这部分给去掉
I had to cut the good-night kiss.
泰德  我想我可以迟到一次...
I think I can be late just once.
-泰德  -我很乐意跟你再来次约会  真的
-Ted  -Look,i would love to have a second date,i would.
但是我明白你现在真的没有时间
But I understand that you really don't have time right now,
-如果你也想跟我约会  给我打个电话好吗  -好的
-But if you ever do,will you give me a call?  -yes.
那好吧
Okay.
就这样  孩子们  这就是我怎么把
And that,kids,is how you turn a "no"
"不行"变成"行"的全过程
Into a "yes."
我的朋友们都告诉我说  艾比  你要坚强点
All my friends told me,"abby,be strong.
他不值得你再给他机会
He doesn't deserve another chance."
-别  别过来  -但是我原谅你!
-No,no,no. -but I forgive you!
不要  不要跟着我啊!
No,no,no,no!
他看起来很友好
he seems nice but then he just kept
但是他却一直在玩弄我的感情
Toying with my emotions.
这个叫泰德的家伙真是个混蛋
This ted guy sounds like a real jerk.
你知道你问题在哪吗
You know your problem?
你太善解人意了
You're too sweet.
-你不是要进去给医生看看你这颗痣吗  -是啊
-Aren't you going to see the doctor about that mole? -oh,yeah.
不过貌似它只是颗聚胺甲烯树脂
Turns out it's just a raisinet.
你想让我带你去一家精美的餐馆吃饭
Hey,how would you like me to take you out to a fancy restaurant
然后去疯狂地购物吗
And then go on a shopping spree?
让你得到应有的享受
Treat you the way you should be treated.
这样会让你忘了泰德那个混蛋吗
Would that make you forget about that ted monster?
我妈妈是错的
My mom was wrong.
纽约这个城市还是会有好男人的
There are nice guys in new york.
我们得先去下我酒店的房间
We just have to go by my hotel room first.
我的床坏了
My bed was broken.
我得去看看他们修好了没有
I just have to make sure they fixed it.
那如果它修好了
Well,then if it's fixed,
我们可不可以先做爱然后再出去购物啊
Can we can have sex on it and then go shopping.
你绝对是我喜欢的类型
I like you.